Guide to the James Wallace Beardsley papers, 1848-1934,
Beardsley, James Wallace papers, 1848-1934
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
James Wallace Beardsley papers, 1848-1934, 1906-1934 (bulk).
2768
James Wallace Beardsley, 1860-1944
.4 cubic ft.
Correspondence, reports, maps and charts, plans and clippings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, reports, maps and charts, plans and clippings concerning irrigation engineering; includes material relating to Puerto Rican dams, and various U.S. dam and irrigation projects. Includes 1848 background report concerning Puerto Rico.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, reports, maps and charts, plans and clippings concerning irrigation engineering; includes material relating to Puerto Rican dams, and various U.S. dam and irrigation projects. Includes 1848 background report concerning Puerto Rico.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Beardsley, James Wallace, 1860-1944.
Subjects:
Irrigation engineering.; Irrigation.; Civil engineers.
Places:
Latin America.; Puerto Rico.
Form and Genre Terms:
Reports.; Maps.; Charts.; Clippings.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Irrigation reports, U.S., 1906-1909 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Mandalay Canal - maps, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Mandalay Canal - maps, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Mandalay Canal - maps, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Puerto Rico irrigation (reports), 1913 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Puerto Rico irrigation projects (correspondence, reports), 1910-1913 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Coama Dam, Puerto Rico (maps), 1913 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Notes on Puerto Rican Irrigation Service, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Sugar beets, Colorado (report), 1914-1915 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Sugar cane projects, 1912-1926 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Irrigation Project Reports, U.S., 1917 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Panama Road Specifications, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Philippine Report, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Dominican Republic Project - reports, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Dominican Republic Project - reports, 1926-1928 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Dominican Republic Project - maps and pamphlet, 1922-1923 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Dominican Republic Project - blueprints, 1926-1927 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Misc. correspondence, 1910-1933 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Clippings, 1915-1934 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Published maps (Box 1, Folder 20)